<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Career on Somewhere in the middle</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/tags/career/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Career on Somewhere in the middle</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 13:30:37 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/tags/career/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Go Back to Fundamental</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-back-to-fundamental/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 04 Nov 2023 13:30:37 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/go-back-to-fundamental/</guid>
      <description>This week, I found myself engrossed in a series of YouTube videos—not the usual technical fare, but rather a collection of career advice and broader insights into software development. It was one of those late-night excursions into the world of online content. After I&amp;rsquo;d concluded my viewing, I decided it was time to call it a night and prepared to retire to bed. Yet, as I lay there, I couldn&amp;rsquo;t shake off the lingering curiosity, so I reached for my trusty iPad and absently refreshed my video suggestions.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Bouncing Back: My Journey from Layoff to Regaining Confidence</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/bouncing-back/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Oct 2023 23:01:16 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/bouncing-back/</guid>
      <description>It has been a month since the unexpected layoff, and my journey to find a new opportunity has been nothing short of challenging. The job market is more competitive than ever, with resume filtering becoming increasingly stringent, making it even harder to secure initial interviews. During this time, I&amp;rsquo;ve encountered a significant shift in the hiring process, with many companies now incorporating competitive programming problems into their assessments.&#xA;While I can&amp;rsquo;t speak for everyone, I want to share my personal experience.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Obliterate the Wave</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/obliterate-the-wave/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 07 Oct 2023 10:31:57 +0700</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/obliterate-the-wave/</guid>
      <description>Working at my previous company had been an incredible journey spanning nearly five years. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t a direct hire but had the privilege of being part of the team through an agency. The company, known for its nurturing work environment, had all the elements conducive to personal and professional growth. The workload was balanced, my co-workers were not just colleagues but friends, and the salary, particularly in a developing country like mine, was more than satisfactory.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
